[
  {
    "type": "book_fact",
    "question": "Which book recorded King Nebuchadnezzar's troubling dream?",
    "answer": "Daniel",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Daniel",
    "chapter": "",
    "verse": "",
    "booknum": "27",
    "uuid": "bc6a848c-20ca-beb9-d5a1-9ecf8a3dc44a",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "character_fact",
    "question": "Who betrayed Jesus?",
    "answer": "Judas Iscariot",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "",
    "chapter": "",
    "verse": "",
    "booknum": "",
    "uuid": "cc89a5f3-7677-8848-4ef5-55b4f3c7d1e7",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "general_trivia",
    "question": "What language was most of the Old Testament originally written in?",
    "answer": "Hebrew",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "",
    "chapter": "",
    "verse": "",
    "booknum": "",
    "uuid": "7db0601e-546a-5435-c858-7f8f3478c2da",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "location_fact",
    "question": "Which land did Abram originally leave to head to the land of Canaan?",
    "answer": "Ur",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "book": "Genesis",
    "chapter": "",
    "verse": "",
    "booknum": "1",
    "uuid": "95bc04ce-fd1f-60f1-7274-88d2630a4430",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "number_fact",
    "question": "How many days did it rain during the flood?",
    "answer": "40",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Genesis",
    "chapter": "",
    "verse": "",
    "booknum": "1",
    "uuid": "9251527b-e459-a0d2-2318-04b06b492c7d",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_complete",
    "question": "In the beginning, God created the _____ and the earth (Genesis 1:1)",
    "answer": "heavens",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Genesis",
    "chapter": "1",
    "verse": "1",
    "booknum": "1",
    "uuid": "9ae828fa-d485-1790-54c9-b272a32f0862",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_complete",
    "question": "And we know that in all things God works for the good of those who love him, who have been called according to his _____ (Romans 8:28)",
    "answer": "purpose",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Romans",
    "chapter": "8",
    "verse": "28",
    "booknum": "45",
    "uuid": "3cc10ebf-0d2e-3c39-cbe4-a50390033242",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_complete",
    "question": "But we have this treasure in _____ to show that this all-surpassing power is from God and not from us (2 Corinthians 4:7)",
    "answer": "jars of clay",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "2 Corinthians",
    "chapter": "4",
    "verse": "7",
    "booknum": "47",
    "uuid": "06caa9b8-eb9a-9d46-7847-10d4e20a72bf",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_complete",
    "question": "Now faith is _____ in what we hope for and assurance about what we do not see (Hebrews 11:1)",
    "answer": "confidence",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Hebrews",
    "chapter": "11",
    "verse": "1",
    "booknum": "58",
    "uuid": "047b8a48-ea10-c8bb-25f0-d774bf3ff607",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_fact",
    "question": "In 2 Corinthians 4:7, what container does Paul say we have treasure in?",
    "answer": "jars of clay",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "2 Corinthians",
    "chapter": "4",
    "verse": "7",
    "booknum": "47",
    "uuid": "2bd03ba3-e779-a88b-4ff5-f8c8cdc52195",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_identify",
    "question": "In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth",
    "answer": "Genesis 1:1",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "book": "Genesis",
    "chapter": "1",
    "verse": "1",
    "booknum": "1",
    "uuid": "b220cec9-3205-d4a6-97fb-2cb5bdd45a54",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_identify",
    "question": "God said to Moses, “I am who I am.This is what you are to say to the Israelites: ‘I am has sent me to you.’”",
    "answer": "Exodus 3:4",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "book": "Exodus",
    "chapter": "3",
    "verse": "4",
    "booknum": "2",
    "uuid": "9e31cc5e-79cf-70b9-60f5-9bb9ad3face0",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_identify",
    "question": "I am a rose of Sharon, a lily of the valleys",
    "answer": "Song of Songs 2:1",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "book": "Song of Songs",
    "chapter": "2",
    "verse": "1",
    "booknum": "22",
    "uuid": "bfaca7e8-80b3-ded1-6b2f-e5189fbf56c8",
    "approved": "Y"
  },
  {
    "type": "verse_identify",
    "question": "But we have this treasure in jars of clay to show that this all-surpassing power is from God and not from us",
    "answer": "2 Corinthians 4:7",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "book": "2 Corinthians",
    "chapter": "4",
    "verse": "7",
    "booknum": "47",
    "uuid": "fe0bc7e6-c92d-c9c5-9fff-47265bf80de6",
    "approved": "Y"
  }
]